<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>MJER Iaido on World MJER Iaido Federation</title>
    <link>https://mjer-iaido.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in MJER Iaido on World MJER Iaido Federation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 23:16:07 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mjer-iaido.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Seito 20th Headmaster and Seito 21st Headmaster</title>
      <link>https://mjer-iaido.github.io/en/post/seito-20th-headmaster-and-seito-21st-headmaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 23:16:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjer-iaido.github.io/en/post/seito-20th-headmaster-and-seito-21st-headmaster/</guid>
      <description>As mentioned above, for a long time, until the Seito 19th Headmaster, the style of Muso Jikiden Eishin-ryu was passed on down the generations without leaving Tosa Province, but at the start of the Showa Era (1926), the Osaka branch of the Dai Nippon Butoku Kai association, recognizing the true value and importance of iaido, advocated its practice along with kendo and judo. From then, the Headmaster was invited from Kochi Prefecture each year, and for around 20 years, he held training sessions that were a great success, with around 20,000 people taking part.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precepts of Master Kōno Hyakuren</title>
      <link>https://mjer-iaido.github.io/en/post/precepts-of-master-k%C5%8Dno-hyakuren/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 00:21:33 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjer-iaido.github.io/en/post/precepts-of-master-k%C5%8Dno-hyakuren/</guid>
      <description>Precepts of Master Kōno Hyakuren, 20 th Head of the Musō-jikiden Eishin-ryu School of Iaido
 
I sincerely hope that those who seek to learn the teachings of this school will maintain throughout their training a firm resolution to correctly transmit to later practitioners the forms of our school that former masters have handed down from ancient times to the present day, absolutely uncolored by personal philosophy and in no way altered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://mjer-iaido.github.io/en/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mjer-iaido.github.io/en/contact/</guid>
      <description>For questions and inquiries, please contact us from the form below.
Your Name / Email address is required. Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>